FINAL PROJECT - QUICK LAUNCH
**My info:
	+ Name: Dieu Ngoc Bao
	+ ID: 1512023
	+ Email: dieungocbao@gmail.com

- What I have done:
	+ User launches the app. An icon  will be added to notification area 
	+ User can right click on it to see menu: Scan to build database, View statitistics, Exit.
	    - Exit menu, of course, will exit the app.
	    - Scan to build database: will scan all exe files in Program Files folder and build a dictionary.
 	    - View statistics: Display chart based on usage frequency of apps. 
	+ Sort app (most used): App is suggested based on priority of recent use.
	+ Use shell to quick launch app
	+ User presses the shortcut key (like Windows + Space), a dialog will appear.
	+ User can select using arrow keys from the list. 
	+ User press enter and the selected app will start. 
- Main flow:
	Example: Type "chorme" in the box, press enter, Chorme will be opened.
			
- Addition flow:
	Example: Type "chme" in the box, the box will not suggest anything. Press enter wont do anything.
		Type "ch" in the box, the box will suggest "chorme" (most used). Press enter. Chorme will be open
- Youtube link: https://youtu.be/fvW0uqxhdfE
- Github link: https://github.com/dieungocbao/Final-QuickLaunch
